const data = [
    {
        question: "What was the Professor's real name? :",
        a: "Ricardo Ramos",
        b: "Sergio Marquina",
        c: "Andres de Fonollosa",
        d: "Agustin Ramos",
        ans: "Sergio Marquina"
        
    },
    {
        question: "Who planned the Bank of Spain heist?",
        a: "The Professor's father",
        b: "The Professor",
        c: "Berlin",
        d: "Palermo",
        ans: "Berlin"
        
    },
    {
        question: "What was the relation between Berlin and The Professor?",
        a: "Best Friend",
        b: "Friend's Brother",
        c: "Real Brother",
        d: "Lovers",
        ans: "Real Brother"
        
    },
    {
        question: "Where did Raquel find The Professor after the first heist?",
        a: "Sri Lanka",
        b: "Maldives",
        c: "Indonesia",
        d: "Thailand",
        ans: "Thailand"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was Gandia?",
        a: "Hostage",
        b: "Robber",
        c: "S.W.A.T",
        d: "Personal Security Guard",
        ans: "Personal Security Guard"
        
    },
    {
        question: "With whom does Berlin get married?",
        a: "Nairobi",
        b: "Tatiana",
        c: "Ariadna",
        d: "Palermo",
        ans: "Tatiana"
        
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of Stockholm's son?",
        a: "Ohio",
        b: "Miami",
        c: "Cincinnati",
        d: "Lisbon",
        ans: "Cincinnati"
        
    },
    {
        question: "How many robbers died till the 2nd heist?",
        a: "Three",
        b: "Four",
        c: "Five",
        d: "Six",
        ans: "Four"
        
    },
    {
        question: "How many people did the professor recruit to help him carry out his plan?",
        a: "Nine",
        b: "Ten",
        c: "Seven",
        d: "Eight",
        ans: "Eight"
        
    },
    {
        question: "How long did the professor take to prepare for the robbery?",
        a: "Years",
        b: "Weeks",
        c: "Months",
        d: "Days",
        ans: "Years"
        
    }
    
];

module.exports = data;